{
    "subject": "Joseph_Heller",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Catch-22",
    "human_readable": "Joseph Heller created Catch-22.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7253782749176025,
            "question": "Who wrote the novel Catch-22?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5729926824569702,
            "question": "When was Catch-22 published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256009101867676,
            "question": "What is the title of the novel created by Joseph Heller?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.482456773519516,
            "question": "Can you describe the main characters in Catch-22?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4748542010784149,
            "question": "What are some of the major themes explored in Catch-22?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4455684721469879,
            "question": "What genre does Catch-22 belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4400387406349182,
            "question": "Has Catch-22 been adapted into other media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3860052824020386,
            "question": "What impact did Catch-22 have on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31282344460487366,
            "question": "Why is Catch-22 considered a classic work of literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2784373462200165,
            "question": "Is Joseph Heller known for writing any famous books?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joseph Heller created Catch-22.",
            "html": "yago_30950_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is Catch-22 considered a classic work of literature?",
            "html": "yago_30950_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Catch-22 have on popular culture?",
            "html": "yago_30950_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Catch-22 been adapted into other media?",
            "html": "yago_30950_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30950_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Joseph Heller created Catch-22.\" Each document mentions Joseph Heller as the author of Catch-22, thereby validating the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}